How do you feel?
I feel great.
You're finally
a part of Yibei.
Welcome.
Good luck.
Should we
start training now?
Wait a minute.
What's wrong?
Take a photo.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
Well done.
You cooperated well.
Am I good?
Good.
What about me?
We cooperated well, right?
You've made progress.
You've decided to go to the competition,
right?
I always feel like I'm missing a sense of touch.
Sometimes I feel the same way.
Both of you
have times when you lack a sense of touch.
What about you?
Practice makes perfect.
So cold.
Fu Binyan,
why are you drinking iced water?
What's going on?
My heart hasn't been feeling well lately.
The ice
can help cool down my neck
and slow down my heart rate.
So you've been carrying a thermos
for ice compresses?
Dipping your face in ice water
is also quite effective.
Why don't you go to the hospital?
My mom has already made an appointment
at a hospital in the capital.
I'll go there
after the next match.
I know my own body.
Don't worry.
But it's a matter of the heart.
What if...
There's no if.
If you're worried about me,
just do your best.
Don't make me too nervous.
Alright.
The next game,
I'll keep an eye on him.
You guys focus on playing.
Let's practice the coordination
we just practiced again.
Okay.
Need a break?
Let's record
our recent practice.
Xu,
I'm sorry.
I can't make it
to the Saturday show.
I have to play
with my teammates.
Alright.
Actually, Jiang Yi
has warned me.
But I just wanted to
hear it from you.
Go ahead.
Good luck with the competition.
We'll see you next time.
I hope there's a next time.
Do you guys feel
Li Haoyu is acting strange today?
He was absent-minded
during the training.
Later,
he took Fu Binyan's cup.
According to his character,
he should be
the most active one.
But recently,
he seems to be preoccupied.
Zhou Yang,
do you know something?
Do you have any other solutions
to that problem?
I think
the auxiliary line
can be drawn somewhere else.
Right?
Aren't you guys
from our basketball team?
Are you
making fun of us?
Not at all.
I'm your fan.
Right, Zhou Yang?
This is Feng Sa,
our class's
sports commissary.
She loves basketball.
She never missed
any of our games.
Thank you.
Enough.
I'm really looking forward to
the next Yudong game.
If you don't train well,
what are you doing sitting here?
Jiang Yi,
we need to talk to you.
It's about Li Haoyu, right?
Go ahead.
Li Haoyu,
come to the gym now.
Now?
What time is it?
What do you want?
[I need to shoot a pre-match video.]
[Remember to wear]
[your coolest outfit.]
[Hurry up.]
Are you kidding?
All my outfits are cool.
What are you doing?
The stage lights aren't even on.
Where is everyone?
Are you kidding me?
What are you
guys doing?
We know
you can't let go of that performance.
So we discussed it
and prepared a
special stage for you.
It was Gu Chenyang's idea.
Time was limited,
so it's not as good as a formal stage,
but make do with it.
How did you get
these instruments
and lights?
Thanks to
Jiang Yi.
Yeah.
She and her cousin
brought all these instruments
from the secret base
for us.
And she also sponsored us with some.
This song was specially composed
by Fang Xu
for the eight of us.
Some of us
even practiced new instruments.
Seniors,
I'll say it first,
I just learned to play the bass.
Don't blame me if I make mistakes.
We won't.
Me too.
You'll be fine.
Okay,
tonight's Pulsar Band's
limited stage
officially begins now.
Pulsar Band!
Pulsar Band, rock and roll!
Yibei, Yibei!
Youth like fire!
Dear audience,
today's focal match
has finally started.
One is this year's
biggest dark horse,
Yibei Middle School.
[the other is the traditional powerhouse,]
[Yudong Middle School.]
[With all the pre-game drama,]
[this is]
[a showdown]
[that everyone's been waiting for.]
Yibei, Yibei,
rise to the sky!
Yudong, Yudong,
who can stop us?
Go!
Yibei, go!
[15 seconds left.]
[Yibei Middle School is down by six points.]
[All five players]
[are pushing themselves to the limit.]
[Will they]
[be able to turn the tide,]
[or are they already exhausted?]
[Coach,]
[we've already lost.]
[But they're still fighting.]
[The referee's whistle blows,]
[and the game is over.]
[Although Yibei Middle School]
[couldn't pull off]
[the final comeback,]
[their fighting spirit today]
[touched everyone present.]
[This team]
[deserves]
[a standing ovation.]
Yudong.
It's okay.
As long as we gave it our all,
we've already won.
Right.
As long as we're always friends,
we're the biggest winners.
Captain!
Idol!
Yibei, come on!
Yibei!
Come on!
Yibei, come on!
Li Haoyu.
Here.
Coming.
Fu Binyan left?
I just sent him off this morning.
He should have arrived by now.
How could he just leave
without saying goodbye?
He doesn't like that kind of scene.
He must have deliberately not said anything.
I was just asking Zhou Yang
if he would come back.
I heard he's preparing to
apply to the music high school
to study violin.
It's hard to meet him again.
Coach Su also left last night.
Where did he go?
He didn't tell me.
Actually,
I have something
to tell you.
What?
Are you leaving, too?
No.
I won't continue
to stay in the basketball club.
I want to prepare for Gaokao.
If so,
I don't want to be
a key player next term.
I'm really exhausted this time.
Next,
I want to work hard
on my band.
Why do you
leave one by one?
Does the Basketball Club
need to recruit again?
Captain
Are you not leaving?
No.
But next semester
we will be busy again.
Oh my god.
I don't even dare to think
what next semester will be like.
Although we don't know,
let's just move forward and see.
Let's take a photo.
It would be nice if Xu Anbo was here.
We could take a group photo.
He went to the snow mountain yesterday.
The photography field trip
will last the whole winter vacation.
By the way,
Chen Song told me
he's aiming to perform
Interstellar Slam Dunk next year.
I'm looking forward to it.
I hope everyone
has found their own path.
Yibei Basketball Club,
we'll meet again.
Let's go.
I've decided
to join the club
as a data analyst.
That's great!
From now on,
Pulsar Band will join us.
Welcome to Yibei Basketball Club.
You can fill in the form
tomorrow.
Sure.
What's wrong?
I'll try it.
It's settled then.
Senior,
how about I give it a try?
Xie Yizhou,
I've officially decided
to transfer to Yibei.
Gu Chenyang,
your training plan
actually works.
What really works
is your perseverance.
Persistence?
Yes.
Persistence.
Captain,
I won't give up.
I'll keep going from now on.